

# **Junior Software Engineer**

0410 485 482 | mark.mekhayl@gmail.com | Sydney, Australia | https://github.com/Lozlink https://www.linkedin.com/in/mark-mekhayl-393834137/ | https://lozlink.github.io/markmekhayl/

#### SUMMARY

A junior developer with 6 years' of prior experience in corporate sales across varying industries. Combining problem solving skills, technical aptitude and and the transferrable skills developed through sales & marketing roles, I have experience in understanding stakeholder needs and would love to apply that creatively in software engineering projects

#### EDUCATION

# SOFTWARE ENGINEERING IMMERSIVE

General Assembly Nov 2022 - Feb 2023

# BACHELOR OF BUSINESS & COMMERCE

Western Sydney University 2013-2017

# SKILLS

Javascript, JQuery

Ruby, Ruby on Rails

SQL

HTML, CSS, SASS

React.js

Node.js

Sinatra

Jest

Git

GitHub

API Integration/Axios

### SOFTWARE ENGINEERING PROJECTS

#### **SPRITE KNIGHT**

- Collaborative web-based game utilizing Node.js, Express.js, and Postgresql
- Built entirely as a Single Page application
- Deployed with Fly.io

#### **BUDGIET**

- A budget tracking tool built using React, Express.js & Postgresql
- Sass & CSS implementation
- API integration using Axios

### EXPERIENCE

#### **SALES & MARKETING MANAGER**

#### **Sunshade Shutters & Blinds**

February 2021 - May 2022

- Managed sales growth by targeting key markets effectively.
- Led targeted marketing campaigns to key demographics via analysis
- Used Data Analysis for market segmentation

# **SALES EXECUTIVE**

## Alsco Australia

November 2019- February 2021

- Proactively targeted demographics through analysis to deliver successful sales results.
- Managed Stakeholder relationships both internally and externally.
- Established relationships with several high profile businesses and worked in tangent with account managers.

#### **BUSINESS DEVELOPMENT CONSULTANT**

#### Staples/Winc Australia

April 2017 - July 2019

- Managed successful sales growth with a focus on Software and Hardware
- Worked in tangent with business units to consistently deliver results.
- Maintained relationships ranging from lower management to executives with companies up to 500 staff.